Jhal
128 Utna Channel, today in this video we will talk about
today's important updates and we will go to
100 about it, on which we have to update our
tablet computer tomorrow, so let's start
first and let's talk, the
global market is coming down today because
it fills up quickly for ₹1,
if you look at this news article of redemption, then
here the Republican
Party wants to stop both the parties which are debt seize
plan, so
looking at this, if there is a loan default in the US,
then you can have a crash in the overall growth market,
so you can understand, right now to
type this, use President
Joe Biden to hold a meeting with some Yes Bank and business leaders,
so that this debt
crisis can be arrested and if we
talk about today's market muscle, today
Nifty is going on and posts
seem to be 81 low and today the bank's team should
wash some white hair here,
if we talk about it now, today also the notification
is big and the Dow Jones
S & P 500
index is the index, in
which there is
500 in the market
And you can earn 1000
[Music]
So
if we talk about any position
and because here subscribe
at 280 here
we get a pin per minute and modern antique
is modern here there is a support back cover
you can see here
after applying a tax the return of Nifty here has solidified a
little bit and later press the existence key
notification because of the touchy hello
we can see here its yes support level current
1716 rate fixed that also a little bit so tomorrow you can
definitely see a little bit simple from here in your mind
that next flight
mode so next and our problem will be to
use 7530 because we will
start taking some profit from the stylish gas
if it increases then you have to continue your test
and you can continue this lead by updating your stop loss which is of a chiffon in these you want to maintain
options in these let me
tell you that above on Plus there is
a use Dr. Soon and above yesterday's extra
oil here above the armor pack
something like this  It is estimated that the current itself is
from Islamic, we have given our tax on the above kilo gas
on Indramani products and options here
through 1770 between call contact shot
pregnancy if you are benefits
then you have to do 10 points here
and today because we use last for boys, then
here you have to do
10 points 3734
[music]
on a person
here for 1 minute, then you have to do some
profit on the apk file or
gas if we
look at the index below five minutes including husband, then
you can calculate like this and
your target will be at least daily
point, so guys, next you have to see
that if you are fooled here then you will only do it,
never
want 37500, please, for 5 minutes
this option will be set, first let me tell you that
we have
a news portal line here in Lee 3017 and phablet canvas,
and even now
we see some open writing at this level, let's
put an event on top  I am using
unwinding because it can be
selected here, so in this
also we will
run some Samsung rate on 30-07-2012, we
should contact 378 through video call,
if you have an option then let me
tell you that if 37.8 is broken then you will only get
one strike on the upper left to
make your bike because if you do
this morning goodbye of 37.10 then
due to this comment you may get some
chances of launch
and you have to pay on the system
that the first topic
here today is the cyclone which belongs to the
medical center, so Vedanta today is more than around
100% profit with 2
hour glass, which is the level taken here again and again, there is a
request again and again, so if it is broken tomorrow then
you can please adopt the network target and a
special significance, if you
can see that there is quantity in it, then
above that there is a support or so Guys
220kV lipstick an hour ago  Here you
must see a profit booking positive of at least 2%.
If you tell me the betting stock limit, then let me
tell you that there is an army band or
a little mistake here, then in this love
attitude and today's project also,
if we do toxin behind the back, then tomorrow
a soldier can do training in it, so guys, the
drama support that was there right now is more than comfortable, for
this we will take our date and
this don't of our profit booking and we
want justice for it, if you are a simple investor then you have to
take a class monitor android and you can
book your profit here, if it
gives you profit above 1%, and if you
liked the video, then definitely like and share it
and you must
subscribe to the channel, such updates are there, first of all, the
price to eat, which is the third
stock, it works for the metal sector
today because there is a huge profit booking in the metal sector,
so you should buy some milk from here,
right now if the market Islam gets a
little tense, then you will get
to see fixed raw stock here today, a lot of stock in metal stocks, hence, today  000 to
profit seventh and printed lowest
level of intent to kill,
click on it here only guys if you have 750
scanner supportive day then tomorrow you are a plant
and that too only time above this
you need Italy situation peace time can create
positive, put that here your
first target will be 420 and the second is if the
insertion is complete then you need easy fonts to make
profit this is your last
off, let it go to the auto sector that
here in the middle there is a user Facebook and and the
top till is different on the tomato and chipset
because of this also there is a celebration here
always, this motor of theirs
was solitaire here on phase for a few days and
when you read this article a little
here,
if
you can take it for 5.5 and in this
and 130
subscribe
this video that's all if you
liked the video then definitely like and if you have not
yet subscribed to our channel
and
you for imp swing and positional traders
What to do, our school on the
link for details, see below, it will rise,
if you want to follow and access our model
and make updates, then
definitely do it, I know
you will not see the video, till then
thank you so much, if UP Nandishwar ji
's
[Music]